They're so beautiful when they're blooming, don't you think?
Huh?
I think we can be together here, okay?
It's pretty private, so no one should see us.
I don't really care about that.
It's not like we're doing anything wrong, you know?
Yeah, but...
But what I do care about is being with you.
That's all I want.
Sumika.
I will never back down on my love.
Oh, Kureha.
I...
I won't either.
Kureha!
A bear!
There's a bear!
No way!
A bear got over the Wall of Severance?
What do we do?
Don't worry, Sumika.
I'm here.
I won't let anything happen to you.
From the beginning, we hated you.
But also, we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you.
So we had to cross the Wall.
Kyuikuma!
Thank you.
Anyways, we'll see you.
Bye!
Growl growl!
Once upon a time, at the far reaches of space,
the minor planet Kumaria exploded.
The fragments of Kumaria that remained
became a meteor swarm that rained down upon the Earth.
That swarm made the world's bears rise up together as one.
Then, they all started attacking humans.
Like, who could have seen that coming, right?
The humans then decided to build the Wall of Severance
in an attempt to drive all the bears, like us,
away from their world.
But guess what?
Silly old man-made rules don't work on bears!
Do the math, humans! Growl!
We are bears! We can't help that!
Bears eat people!
That's kind of like our thing!
And so...
Everyone, starting today you'll have some new friends.
This is Ginko Yurishiro and Lulu Yurigasaki.
Let's give them a warm welcome.
Growl!
We supposedly transferred here,
but they don't know what we are
because we're disguised as humans.
He-he!
Looks like nobody can tell we're bears so far!
So many girls for Lulu to pick from!
Sniff, sniff!
It's heaven!
The whole room smells delicious, Growl!
This is perfect!
Lulu is going to work hard so she can eat lots of girls!
You too, right, Ginko?
Oh, have you met Ginko Yurishiro yet?
She's a bear too, of course.
She's Lulu's darling and Lulu loves her
and loves her to bits and bits and bits!
Now then, girls, I'm sure most of you have heard the news already.
But unfortunately, a couple of bears were sighted this morning
on the roads very close to this school.
I realize this is a shock.
We considered it unthinkable for bears to cross the Wall of Severance
and enter the human world.
The warning has since been lifted,
but you still need to be very careful.
Even inside the school, make sure you're never alone.
You should always have a friend with you.
There she is!
I finally found her.
Yeah, I like how that girl smells.
I bet she's delicious.
Slurp!
That Patty?
They say something!
Before you are out and come over,
I have to ask her any questions.
Someone likes me,
I am sorry,
we're going out of the taboon!
Uhh, uhh.
Sumika?
OK, sorry, let's go.
tom Exactly...
There it be,
eh,
N livestream...
Hey, Kureha. What do you like in your lunchbox?
My lunchbox? Why?
Well, I like chikawa fried and sui tempura. I was just wondering what you preferred.
Let's see. I guess spaghetti and shiokara.
Shiokara? Seriously?
Is that weird?
What? It's just, you like what old men eat.
Old men? Yeah.
That's not very nice. I mean, yeah, maybe it smells a little when I open my lunchbox, but so what?
I love it.
What?
I don't care if you've got the palate of an old man. I love you anyway.
I love you so much. And I always will.
Sumika?
Sumika!
Kureha? Hey! Is something wrong?
No. I just...
Oh no! Did you not get to eat lunch?
No.
Here.
Let's eat together. We can each take a half.
There's chikawa in this roll, isn't there?
Yeah, but it's not fried and tempura.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
You know, I think we should eat here every day from now on.
You mean it? Really?
Yeah. I want to eat with you.
I think food tastes better when we're together anyway. Do you think that too?
I do.
Growl, growl, growl, growl, growl.
Growl, growl, growl.
Lulu is practically starving right now.
Oh, she smells so yummy. I want to eat that girl.
Growl, growl.
You are such a glutton, Ginkgo.
But that's okay because Lulu will always love you.
You can sink your teeth in Lulu anywhere you'd like.
Come on, you can even do it now.
Oh, Lulu can't believe she's saying this to you.
Lulu feels so vulnerable when she's around you, Ginkgo.
The storm chased us down.
This is only the beginning.
A warning that it'll start with what's most precious.
The invisible storm will destroy whatever is in its path
until we're worn away into nothing.
Kureha, I'll never back down on my love either.
What?
You said it earlier, that you wouldn't give up on me.
Well, I won't give up on you either.
I won't give up on love.
Our love.
Growl, growl, growl.
Lulu's so hungry she doesn't think she can take much more.
Growl, growl.
I cannot get over that delicious smell.
I still feel the same way.
I won't back down.
I promise I'll protect you, Sumika.
I believe you.
I knew it.
I had a feeling you'd been caught up in the invisible storm too.
You have, haven't you, Kureha?
Mitsuko.
It's cruel to cut down flowers,
especially when they're in full bloom.
It's the invisible storm.
It destroys beautiful, kind things first.
Yes, but this time what it's done has made up my mind.
I can't just sit here and keep letting these things happen.
Kureha, Sumika, let's stop the storm.
We can take a stand together.
I know I'm the class representative,
but I'm ashamed of myself for not having taken a stand against it already.
Sumika, I'm so sorry.
Do you think you can ever forgive me?
For what?
There's nothing to forgive.
Thank you for saying that.
And you know, I think we could be the best of friends.
I bet we can stop the invisible storm.
As long as we're working together, why couldn't we?
But I think we should go home for the day now.
There's still that bear warning.
I say, early tomorrow morning, we come back here.
Then the flower bed can get fixed.
I don't mind helping you at all.
Oh no, your hand!
No, it's okay.
This just means I'm one of you.
And that we're friends.
Who did that?
Lulu's so happy she got to eat a lily.
Lulu wants to eat that girl.
Who do you mean by that girl?
Let's go on trial now.
Yeah, let's go!
Yeah!
Kareha, did you have fun with your friend again today?
Yep!
Guess what, Mom?
We ate snacks together at lunch!
Great!
Were they yummy?
Mm-hmm!
Everything tastes better when I get to eat them with her.
Aw, you really love her, don't you, sweetie?
Yeah, I do!
Yes, and that's why this time the one I love will be safe.
I'll protect her with my own hands.
I'll never forgive the bears.
I'll ruin them.
Every one...
Oh!
Unit 103, we're at the flower bed in the Arashigaoka High School Courtyard.
Lots of bear friends here, and blood stains.
Looks like there was a Vic.
We found her a fax at the scene.
She may be a student.
We're still searching the area, though.
Yes, we were supposed to meet here.
We were...
We were gonna come early and fix up the flower bed.
Your call has been forwarded to an automatic voicemail system.
The mobile customer you are trying to reach is currently...
I heard they found a shoe on the ground.
They did?
You know what that means.
Apparently, she came in early to try and fix up that flower bed.
Oh, gosh.
It's so hard to believe.
It's really her own fault for going alone.
To survive, we need to make sure we have friends.
Yeah, you're right.
There's no other way.
Uh-huh.
The next invisible storm's coming.
She's to blame since she wasn't being invisible.
To the bears, we're just weak prey.
We have to stay with the herd.
No matter what.
Exactly.
The mood of the herd is what's most important.
It's not true.
It can't be!
I refuse to believe Sumika was eaten.
Hello?
Sumika?
Is your love the real thing?
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance.
Kareha Tsubaki.
If your love is true,
go to the roof immediately.
The bears are waiting for you.
What do you mean?
Is Sumika okay?
Give yourself over to the bears and your love will be approved.
The time for judgment has come.
Growl, growl.
Sumika!
Give her back to me!
We want to eat that girl!
We want to eat her right this minute!
This court is now in session!
Welcome to Severance Court.
The door has opened, so enter what we consider the land of enlightenment for all living things.
Yes, even human and bear.
We shall now pass judgment for the sake of humans and bears.
Life sexy!
For humans and bears, life cool!
For humans and bears, life beauty!
Let the Yuri Trial begin!
Defendant bears, do you admit that you are in fact criminal bears?
Growl!
Yeah, but we can't be held responsible because we're so hungry all the time!
And we won't back down on our love ever, growl growl!
Your Honor, humans and bears have a barrier separating them called the Wall of Severance,
and it is not to be crossed.
The defendants have crossed it anyway, infiltrating the world of the humans.
This is obvious and blatant overeating.
Therefore, they are guilty!
Sparkle!
Your Honor, the only thing blatant here is the Prosecutor's hostile attitude towards bears!
Counsel, was that intended to be an objection?
I mean, yeah, even bears have to eat to live!
That is the way of the universe!
Tell me, do you seriously expect these poor bears to starve to death?
But, Your Honor, if we admit the defendants' appeal, we can expect more human lives to be lost!
Objection!
He's showing undue favor towards humans!
Sustained!
Keep in mind, this court must act as a scale that weighs both worlds impartially,
for that is sexy shabba-da-doo!
Sparkle!
Growl, thank you!
So that means we've got permission to eat her, right, Your Honor?
Objection!
Your Honor, please!
We ask you grant the defendants a love judgment!
Very well.
Defendant bears, I ask you, do you want to be invisible?
Or, would you rather eat humans?
We'll eat!
Bring on the humans!
Growl, growl!
I am now ready to declare the verdict.
Yuri, approved!
Growl, growl, growl!
You're in!
Ah-hoo!
Dang!
Growl, growl, growl, growl, growl, growl!
Growl, growl, growl!
All right.
What?
Kureha!
I, Ginkgo, am going to eat you!
Korea I think I'm going to eat you I can't find what I'm searching for I can't
find it I've been searching in the invisible storm searching for what
searching for it where give it to me the promise kiss
thank goodness you're finally awake Mitsuko hey where are we the nurse's
office what why something happened we found you passed out on the roof we don't
know she hasn't been found yet oh no he said the bears on the roof would give
her back please calm down when we found you we
didn't see anyone else up there just me but how I'll be right back I'm gonna go
get you something hot to drink was it just a dream no it had to have been real
Oh Sumika be okay please
what's that sound it's someone over there vandalizing the flower bed again
I don't care if it's a crime
grub grub I won't allow it to know what
those are the transfer students I get it they've transformed they're only
pretending to be human
sleep